<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xml" href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xslt.xml"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.3.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-05-08T21:04:30+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000//</id><entry><title type="html">Evan Sheridan</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/people/first-post/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Evan Sheridan" /><published>2016-11-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2016-11-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/people/first-post</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/people/first-post/">&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Research: it is well known that Quantum Monte Carlo simulations are plagued
 with numerical and statistical errors. The goal of my current research is to
 try and minimise some of these errors so that that Dynamincal Mean Field
 Theory (DMFT) calculations (i) become more accurate and (ii) converge faster.
 To that end,  I am developing impurity solvers for the Dynamical Mean Field Theory.
 With a broader view in mind, I am aiming to use these solvers to investigate
 the equation of state for strongly correlated systems.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Publications:&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Recent conference attended:&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><summary type="html">PhD Student</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hello World!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/first-post/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hello World!" /><published>2016-11-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2016-11-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/first-post</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/first-post/">&lt;p&gt;It is terribly mundane to entitle my first post “Hello World!” but this is
probably the only time in which it has ever had some real meaning. I
suppose “initial commit” could also qualify but that is rather pessimistic since
I have still some semblance of hope that this blog will be read by somebody other
than me (which is currently not the case for the majority of my git repos…must be
that .f90 extension…).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To cut a long story short I hope to regularly contribute here about things that I find
interesting: which will range from my research, what I am reading (academically
and otherwise), what projects I am working on in my spare time to how to do cool
things with python and maybe even fortran if you are lucky!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, stay tuned - ideas are brewing! And on that note: “Goodbye World”.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="PhD" /><summary type="html">What it says on the tin...</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/%7B%22feature%22=%3Enil%7D" /></entry></feed>
